SEAN ANDERSON

BSc Web Design & Development

Curriculum Vitae

STATEMENT.....

A resourceful and practical Graduate Designer driven to personally achieve against challenging targets and deadlines whilst maintaining quality standards even if under demanding pressure.

I have constantly adapted to any new environment and have rapidly forged strong internal relationships. I have become more commercially astute through my work experience and education. I have a variety of experience which I am keen to further develop.

SKILLS & EXPERIENCE.....

Customer Services

IT Helpdesk Experience

Communication

Design and Graphics

Cash Handling

Handling Stock

Creativity

Team Work

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS.....

- -Practical experience of PDMS, Office 365 Software, Linux System Administration and IT Helpdesk software.
- -Practical experience of Software Development including the use of PHP, SQL, |avascript and |query.
- -Self-taught programming languages including Python.
- -Experience working as part of a team to develop a business plan and website promoting research group 'Roslin Cells.'
- -Part of the team which won the 2010 Scottish Schools Open Boys Cup (Arbroath High School) and part of multiple Division I Club Basketball teams.

INTERESTS & HOBBIES.....

Travelling I enjoy travelling and experiencing new places. I have had experiences living as an expat which allowed me to expand my knowledge of other cultures.

Sports I am was part of the Arbroath Basketball team - The Musketeers - and

spend time running to keep fit.

Music I spend time listening to music and will often attend concerts.

REFERENCE.....

Steve McGinnis

Manager Dundee City Council

Email: steve.mcginnis@dundeecity.gov.uk
Address: Dundee City Council, 50 N Lindsay St,
Dundee DDI IQE, United Kingdom



II Keptie Mews, Arbroath, DDII 3EQ



seananderson10@hotmail.co.uk | 07530221573

full driving license

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

PDMS	Equipment & Piping Design	2015
Bachelor of Sciences Abertay University, UK	Web Design & Development	2013-15
Higher National Diploma Angus College, UK	Interactive Media & Web Design	2011-13
Scottish Highers Arbroath High School, UK	English, Chemistry, Mathematics, Physics, Graphic Communications	2009-1

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Assistant IT Officer

Dundee City Council, Scotland, UK

2022-2024

PHP development & migration, Suse Linux system management & administration, Meet SLA's for helpdesk tickets in Halo ITSM, SQL database management, Network administration.

Working with the council gave me valuable experience working in software development while also helping users though the IT helpdesk meeting SLA's while also migrating, developing and fixing PHP applications from an old mainframe on to newer machines.

Machine Tester

NCR, Dundee, UK

2021 - 2022

Working with Pertemps for the client NCR has given me some insight into the work being done and processes at NCR through jobs on their ATM machines but also the hands-on environment around the labs.

Bar Tender/Waiter 2019 - 2021 Coast (Restaurant), Arbroath, UK 2015 - 2016

Customer service, cash handling, stock handling, serving food and beverages, maintaining restaurant's high standard of cleanliness, responsibility to open and close the restaurant.

Web Developer

Freelance, UK

2018 - Present

I have committed myself to practicing and applying a range of coding languages. I have been working on small projects including building a website for local business 'Wee Weddin' Hoose' based in Arbroath.

Kitchen Designer

Wren Kitchens, Dundee, UK

2017 - 2018

Skills developed: Customer Service, Creativity, Product Knowledge, Problem Solving, Target Setting, Working to Health & Safety Standards, Working to British Standards, Creating Practical Solutions, Using a range of software to create plans and renders (CGIs) to present to clients.

Bar Tender/Waiter 2016 - 2017
The Old Boatyard Restaurant, Arbroath 2012 - 2013

Part time employment during education and following graduation.

Bar Tender

Westport Bar, Arbroath, UK

2014 - 2015

Worked as part of a team to provide customers with desired food and beverages.

Machine Operator

Interplex PMP, Arbroath, UK

2011

Worked weekend shifts until extra demand was met. As a part time operator, two I2-hour shifts were worked per week (both night shift). This gave me experience working both long shifts and late hours while keeping up with production.